Frederick Loewe Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-9)
  - Show Music
    - Great lady, 1938, Lyrics by Earl Crooker (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; [15] p., Titles include: Transition scenes 6-7 act I; I can see myself in the theatre; Madame is at home; Incomplete, portions damaged and removed (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Unidentified
        - Piano score; p. 5-7, “Tempo di marcia” on top of p. 5 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Fragments
        - "Madame at home" piano-vocal score; p. 18, Sketch on verso (Box-folder 4/17)
        - "I'll take my love" piano-vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 4/17)
    - The life of the party, 1942, Lyrics by Earl Crooker; Includes songs from a 1930 film of the same title, and the show Salute to spring, 1937 (Box 4)
      - Here we go again
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., Lyrics by Raymond Knight (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Life of the party
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p., Cover is p. 4; crossed out section on p. 1 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - One robin doesn't make a spring
        - Lead sheet/piano-vocal score; [2] p., This score may have been part of Salute to spring materials; p. [1] caption: Scene I/Elinor-Bessie (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Wearin' the grin
        - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; Crossed out, unidentified measure of short score on verso (Box-folder 4/21)
    - The little prince, 1974 film, Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner (Box 4)
      - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score, Bound ozalids; Titles include: I need air; Matters of consequence; I’m on your side; Be happy; You’re a child; I never met a rose; Why is the desert; A snake in the grass; Closer and closer; Closer and closer and closer; Little Prince; unidentified (Box-folder 4/22)
    - My fair lady, 1956, Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner (Box 5)
      - Ascot gavotte
        - Piano-vocal score; 3 p., Paper heavily stained (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Come to the ball
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p., Not used (Box-folder 5/2)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 11 p., Annotations (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Dear little fool
        - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; not used (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Embassy waltz
        - Piano score; 8 p., p. 1-5 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Entr’acte
        - Piano score; 8 p., p. 2-8 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Flower market
        - Piano score/piano-vocal score; 5 p., Includes reprise of “Wouldn’t it be loverly” (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Get me to the church on time
        - Piano-vocal score; [5] p., p. A-3 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/8)
      - A hymn to him
        - Piano-vocal score; 13 p. (Box-folder 5/9)
      - I could have danced all night
        - Piano-vocal score; 7 p., Inside cover crossed out p. 3-4 of early version “Why can’t the English”; p. 3-7 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/10)
      - I'm an ordinary man
        - Piano-vocal score; 13 p., 2 m. addition taped to bottom of p. 13 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - I've grown accustomed to her face
        - Piano-vocal score; 13 p., Soliloquy; heavily stained (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Just you wait
        - Piano-vocal score; 8 p., Crossed out note on cover p.: Att. Franz [Allers]: Julie maybe Eb? Please try (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Lady Liza
        - Lead sheet; 1 p. (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Liza-counter
        - Lead sheet; 2 p., Not used; Music related to "The embassy waltz" (Box-folder 5/15)
      - On the street where she lives
        - Piano-vocal score; 7 p., Inside cover crossed out p. 7-8 of early version “Why can’t the English”; p. 1-3, 6-7 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Overture
        - Piano score; [2] p., Heavily stained; p. [1] caption: Have [Robert] Russell [Bennett] confirm keys/ into 1 Refr. “Street” into 1 Refr. “Danced”/”Street” in C/Danced in Eb/into Opening in C (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Please don't marry me
        - Lead sheet; 3 p., Not used; The music is a precursor to “What do the simple folk do?" from Camelot (Box-folder 5/18)
      - The Pygmalion waltzes
        - Piano score; 7 p., Includes Finale I/Embassy waltz (Box-folder 5/19)
        - Holograph piano score; 4 p., Annotations; p. 1 caption: Andre [Previn]–I suggest (Box-folder 5/20)
      - The rain in Spain
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p., Crossed out 2 m. on verso of p. 3 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - The servants chorus
        - Piano-vocal score; [2] p., p. [1] caption: Alan [Jay Lerner]–call Moss [Hart]/How many verses?? (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Show me
        - Piano-vocal score; 7 p., Heavily stained; Inside cover crossed out p. 5-6 of early version “Why can’t the English” (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Shy
        - Piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 5/23)
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p., Not used; The two versions have variant accompaniments (Box-folder 5/23)
      - There's a thing called love
        - Lead sheet; 2 p., Not used; Laid in: typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 5/24)
      - What is a woman?
        - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; not used (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Why can't the English? see also covers for I could have danced all night, On the street where she lives and Show me
        - Piano-vocal score; 10 p., Inside cover crossed out p. 1-2 of early version “Why can’t the English”; p. 1-4 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/26)
      - With a little bit of luck
        - Piano-vocal score; 6 p., p. 2-4 heavily stained (Box-folder 5/27)
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p., In German (Box-folder 5/28)
      - Without you
        - Piano-vocal score; 7 p., Heavily stained (Box-folder 5/29)
      - Wouldn't it be loverly see also Flower market
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p., Heavily stained (Box-folder 5/30)
      - You did it: opening act II
        - Piano-vocal score; 23 p. (Box-folder 5/31)
      - Synopsis of musical numbers
        - Piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 5/32)
      - Vocal selections; 30 p. (Box-folder 5/33)
      - Souvenir program, With Edward Mulhare and Pamela Charles as the leads (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Paint your wagon, 1951, Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner (Box 6)
      - Finale ultimo
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p., “Gloria in excelsius, Deo!” on cover; this bears no relation to the “Finale ultimo” published in the score (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Growing pains see Muchee good world
      - Hand me down that can o' beans
        - Piano-vocal score; 12 p. (Box-folder 6/2)
      - How can I wait?
        - Piano-vocal score; 7 p., Laid in: typescript lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 6/3)
      - I still see Eliza see also A pebble in a stream
        - Piano-vocal score; 3 p., Pencil sketch continues onto verso p. 3; Early version of accompaniment erased through most of song; Inside last p. of cover has crossed out title: A pebble in a stream (Box-folder 6/4)
      - I talk to the trees
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p., Laid in: typescript lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 6/5)
      - I'm on my way
        - Piano-vocal score; 7 p., Crossed out lead sheet, no lyric, for “Wait for me” verso p. 1 (Box-folder 6/6)
        - Piano score; [2] p., Introduction (Box-folder 6/6)
        - Lead sheet; 12 p., For Sam; no lyric (Box-folder 6/6)
        - Choral arrangement; 2 p., Unknown hand (Box-folder 6/6)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 16 p., Annotations in pencil (Box-folder 6/6)
      - In between
        - Piano-vocal score; 10 p. (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Julio's song see Sh!
      - Mormon's prayer see Trio
      - Movin'
        - Piano-vocal score; 8 p., Crossed out music on versos of p. 1, 2 and 6 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Muchee good world, Not used
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 6/10)
        - Piano score; 3 p., Crossed out sketch for “Growing pains” on verso of p. 3 (Box-folder 6/10)
        - Piano-vocal score; p. 1, 2A, 2B, 3-9, No lyric (Box-folder 6/10)
        - Lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 6/10)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; p. 4-8, Annotations in pencil (Box-folder 6/11)
      - A pebble in a stream see I still see Eliza and A pebble in a stream
      - Say hello for me
        - Piano-vocal score; 2 p., Not used (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Sh!
        - Piano-vocal score; 4 p., No lyric; not used; Crossed out sketch for “Julio’s song” on verso p. 3 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - The strike
        - Piano score/lead sheet; 10 p., Substantially different from published version (Box-folder 6/14)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Take the wheels off the wagon
        - Piano-vocal score; 1 p., Verse; burn mark on paper (Box-folder 6/16)
      - There's a coach comin' in!
        - Piano-vocal score; 10 p. (Box-folder 6/17)
        - Choral score; 14 p. (Box-folder 6/18)
      - They call the wind Maria
        - Choral score; 3 p. (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Trio, Alternate title: Mormon's prayer
        - Piano-vocal score; 2 p., Incomplete (Box-folder 6/20)
        - Choral score; 3 p. (Box-folder 6/20)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Annotations (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Wait for me see I'm on my way
      - Whoop-ti-ay!
        - Piano-vocal score; 10 p. (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Folders which contained above scores, titled in Loewe’s hand (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Piano-vocal score; 260 p., Laid in sketches/doodles in ink; [3] p., 1 p. blank (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Petticoat fever, 1934, Lyrics by Irene Alexander (Box 7)
      - Love tiptoed through my heart
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Salute to spring, 1937, Lyrics by Earl Crooker (Box 7)
      - April day
        - 2 piano-vocal scores; 5 p. each (Box-folder 7/3)
      - It's extraordinary
        - Lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 7/4)
      - One robin
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Salute to spring
        - Piano-vocal score; 5 p., Annotations in pencil (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Set to music
        - Lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Lead sheets and sketches; [28] p., Titles include: Once upon a time/Bessie's theme; Somehow; It's a very charming spot; A waltz was born in Vienna; Opera; unidentified (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Songlist; [1] p. (Box-folder 7/9)
    - What's up, 1943, Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner (Box 7)
      - A girl is like a book
        - Piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 7/10)
      - How fly times
        - Piano-vocal score; 2 p., Incomplete (Box-folder 7/11)
      - The ill-tempered clavichord
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 11 p., Annotations in pencil; Upper right corner of p. 1 torn off (Box-folder 7/12)
        - Holograph piano-vocal score, 2 photocopies; 9 p. each; Laid in: folder (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Three girls in a boat
        - Piano-vocal score; 1 p., No lyric (Box-folder 7/13)
      - You wash and I'll dry
        - Sketch; [1] p., Music is significantly different from published version; Unidentified sketches in pencil on verso; [1] p. (Box-folder 7/14)
      - You're easy to get along with
        - Lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 7/13)
      - You've got a hold on me
        - 2 piano-vocal scores; 5 p. each (Box-folder 7/15)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., No lyric; Caption: Gloria Warren (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Unidentified Show (Box 7)
      - Prologue
        - Piano-vocal score; p. 1-9, 12, 14-23, 26-29, 33-36, Includes sung portions: Boola, boola; My song is a sigh; Prosit, prosit; One, two, three; Eins, zwei, drei; Also includes characters of a Policeman, Agnes and Antonia, and mentions of Vienna and horse racing. There is a crossed out sketch on verso of p. 7; p. 15 has lyrics on verso, and 4 additional m. taped to the recto; sketches for “Prosit, prosit” on the versos of p. 16-17; a crossed out sketch on the verso of p.23; p. 33 is described as “Finale” (Box-folder 7/16)
      - One-two-three, Lyrics by Charles Locke
        - Piano-vocal score; 1 p., Verse only (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Untitled
        - Piano score; p. 12-13 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Walking theme and chorus
        - Condensed score/piano-vocal score and sketch; p. 8-9, Lyrics for “Prosit, prosit” in German (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Dance specialty
        - Piano score; p. 33, Mentions insert of “Refrain of One-two-three” (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Untitled
        - Piano score; p. 33 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - The best of Lerner and Loewe, Published songbook; 160 p.; Titles include: You wash and I’ll dry; You’ve got a hold on me; The day before spring; God’s green world; I love you this morning; Almost like being in love; Brigadoon; From this day on; The heather on the hill; There but for you go I; Another autumn; I still see Elisa; I talk to the trees; I’m on my way; Sh!; They call the wind Maria; Wand’rin’ star; Get me to the church on time; I could have danced all night; I’ve grown accustomed to her face; On the street where you live; The rain in Spain; With a little bit of luck; Wouldn’t it be loverly; Camelot; Follow me; How to handle a woman; I loved you once in silence; If ever I would leave you; The lusty month of May; The earth and other minor things; Gigi; I remember it well; I’m glad I’m not young anymore; In this wide, wide world; The night they invented champagne; Thank heaven for little girls (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Non-Show and Unidentified Music
    Arranged alphabetically by song title.
    - Barcarolle see Multiple titles
    - Ballad
      - Lead sheet 2 p., No lyric; Crossed out sketches on verso of p. 2 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - The barrendero, 1942, Lyrics by James Tranter
      - Piano-vocal; p. 3-10 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Piano-vocal; 7 p. (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Bedrooms, Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner
      - Piano-choral/short score; 6 p. (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Blues in 3/4 time see also item in Unmatched numbered pages
      - Piano score; [1] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Capriccio
      - Piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Cath’rine!, 1925, Lyrics by Leo Lelievre, Varna and Rouvray
      - Piano-vocal score; [1] p., Incomplete; Fragile; page taped together (Box-folder 8/6)
    - A chair at the table
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/7)
    - The clever worm
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., Described as “Scene I/Arts and Mrs. Rooney” (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Every time see Multiple titles
    - Finale
      - Piano score/piano-vocal score; 3 p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/9)
    - First I act ballet
      - Piano score; 3 p. (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Gaily I sin
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., On verso: "Kitchen song" lead sheet in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Gallop, Alternate title: Don't gallop in your night shirt
      - Piano score; [1] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Growin' pains see also Muchee good world from Paint your wagon
      - Lead sheet; 2 p., No lyric; "Verse" on verso of p. 1 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Sketches; [1] p., 1 sketch crossed out (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Sketch; [1] p., Crossed out (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Heidi
      - Sketch; [1] p., Dated 1965 August (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Hollywood/51
      - Sketches; [3] p. (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Hour glass waltz see Untitled pieces
    - I wish I were your wife
      - Lead sheet; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/16)
    - If we could have met in 1929, Lyrics by Earl Crooker
      - Piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Just then
      - Piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Kitchen song see Gaily I sin
    - Let no man say that the Lord does wrong
      - Sketches; [1] p. (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Limehouse
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Little rendezvous
      - Piano score; [2] p., At top of p. [1] “Act I No. 4" (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Love bower see also Where's my wife from The day before spring
      - Lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Love is blind, 1924, Lyrics by Alfred Du Bynne (Al Dubin)
      - Piano-vocal score, Published; p. 3-5; Missing cover (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Piano accompaniment arrangement; p. [1] only (Box-folder 8/23)
    - The mosquito see Two concert etudes
    - My family interferes with me
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., Incomplete lyric; Unidentified p. 2 of piano score on verso, along with p. 3 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Night after night
      - Lead sheet; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/25)
    - The night can be blind
      - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., Sections sung by Linkmen and Officers (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Over your head
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., Lyric suggests this may have been for Gigi or The little prince (Box-folder 8/27)
    - The party of the second part
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., Caption title: Jullio Carminat... (Box-folder 8/28)
    - A pebble in a stream
      - Piano score; 9 p., May have been for Paint your wagon; Laid in: folder (Box-folder 8/29)
    - Piano concerto for the left hand
      - Piano score; [1] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Quartette
      - Piano-choral score; p. 1-3, versos p. 11-13, In two segments, the lyrics for the first begins “The rose cannot bloom/Amid the winter’s gloom...” and the second “My song is a sigh for lips I’ve never kissed...” (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Rhumba see Multiple titles
    - Riviera
      - Sketch; [1] p., Unidentified sketches above and below (Box-folder 8/32)
    - Sag’ ja..., 1923, Lyrics by Ernst Neubach
      - Piano-vocal score; 5 p., Fragile (Box-folder 8/33)
    - Say hello for me see What's to become of me?
    - Sehr wichtig!!
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; On verso: Important! (Box-folder 8/34)
    - Someone will love you
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/35)
    - The son of a wooden soldier, 1941, Lyrics by John W. Bratton
      - Piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 8/36)
    - The spider and the fly see Two concert etudes
    - The streetsweeper see The barrendero
    - There's always one you can't forget see also What's to become of me?
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; Probably for Gigi or My fair lady (Box-folder 8/37)
    - To whom it may concern, 1942, Lyrics by Earl Crooker
      - Piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 8/38)
    - Two see Multiple titles
    - Two concert etudes for the piano: The spider and the fly; The Mosquito, 1943, Lyrics by Earl Crooker
      - Piano score; 6 p. (Box-folder 8/39)
    - The undeserving poor
      - Sketches; [1] p., Probably for My fair lady (Box-folder 8/40)
    - Valse
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; incomplete; “Long waltz” on verso and below title (Box-folder 8/41)
    - Vienna will sing again
      - Short score; 5 p. (Box-folder 8/42)
      - Piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 8/42)
    - Wait for me
      - Piano-vocal score; 6 p., Crossed out score on verso of p. 3 (Box-folder 8/43)
    - What's to become of me?, Probably for My fair lady
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; Written at bottom: There’s always one (Box-folder 8/44)
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., Titled: Say hello for me; No lyric (Box-folder 8/44)
      - Sketches; [1] p. (Box-folder 8/44)
    - Who is the lady?
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric; 2 unidentified sketches on verso (Box-folder 8/45)
    - Ya, ya, ya, they never go home
      - Lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 8/46)
    - Multiple titles
      - Lead sheet; 4 p., No lyric; Titles include: Two; Every time; Barcarolle; Rhumba (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Sketches; [1] p., Numbered 10, 11 and 12 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Untitled pieces
      - Piano score; p. 10-17, Includes “Hour glass waltz” and mentions characters Hugo and Antonia (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Piano score; p. 2-4, Includes note to “copy Invitation,” possibly for The day before spring (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Lead sheet; p. 2-3, 6 m. sketch on verso of p. 2 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Piano score; p. 4-6 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Piano score; p. 2-6 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Condensed score/sketch; [1] p., Sketches for accompaniment figures on verso (Box-folder 9/8)
      - String quartet/4 part arrangement; [2] p. (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Violin part(?); [2] p., Refers to "One step" (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Condensed score/sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 9/8)
      - 3 lead sheets; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Unmatched numbered pages
      - Piano score; p. 1, 3 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Lead sheet; p. 2, No lyric (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score/short score; p. 2, Mentions “Curtain” probably part of an overture (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score; p. 3, Crossed out piano score on verso (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano-vocal score; p. 3, Lyrics are “...more than I did last night.” (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score; p. 4 see also Blues in 3/4 time (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score; p. 4 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score; p. 5, Mentions “Interlude,” “Chorus (vocal)” and “dance”; crossed out sketches on verso (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano-vocal score; p. 6, Lyrics are “...So my heart will beat for you and me.” (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score; p. 6, 4 m. sketch on verso (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Piano score; p. 10-11, Includes “Entrance of horse (dance),” crossed out section with lyric “alone without you,” and section titled “Gavotte” (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Miscellaneous sketches and fragments; 14 leaves (Box-folder 9/10)
- Miscellaneous Personal Papers (Box 10, 13)
  - Personal correspondence, 10 letters and cards; Includes a 2 p. telegram from Josh Logan, 1966 March 11 expressing his enthusiasm for working with Loewe on Camelot; empty envelopes laid in at back (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Notes in Loewe's hand, 12 items including envelopes, and a photocopy; some appear to be telephone messages and notes, 1 item appears to be a piano recital repertoire, 1 is a draft of a letter declining an honorary degree, and, most significantly is the first page of a talk about his association with Alan Jay Lerner (Box-folder 10/2)
  - ASCAP certificate, signed by Morton Gould and Stanley Green, 1970 Sept. 17 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Eulogy by Red Skelton, Photocopy of annotated typescript; 6 p. (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Various programs, invitations and tickets for Loewe related events; 7 items (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Admissions information for Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation (Box-folder 10/6)
  - “A time of social transfusion”; odd writing, may be in Loewe’s hand; [1] p. (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Kennedy Center Honors 1985: bound item including: calendar, photographs, bios (Box-folder 10/8)
  - “Kennen Sie den?”; typed anecdote in German (Box-folder 10/9)
  - On the street where I live; proof copy of Alan Jay Lerner’s autobiography (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Loewe’s New York office telephone book, disbound, approximately 330 p. (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 13/3)
- Photographs (Box 11)
  - FL portraits, 7"x9" (2)e (Box-folder 11/1)
  - FL standing with basket, 5"x10", right half torn off (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Photocopy of FL at piano (Box-folder 11/3)
  - FL with Alan Jay Lerner, 8"x10" (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Photos of portraits of FL by James Montgomery Flagg (2), 1 of unidentified woman ( 1946 ), possibly wife Ernestine Zwerleine (Box-folder 11/5)
  - FL shaking hands with unidentified man, 8"x10" (Box-folder 11/6)
  - FL horseback riding, 8"x10" (3), 2 with unidentified woman (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Snapshots ca. 1963-1965, including FL on horse (3) (Box-folder 11/8)
  - FL with unidentified at formal party, 8"x10" (2) (Box-folder 11/9)
  - FL receiving plaque and smashing target, 8"x10" (2) (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Snapshots of FL with unidentified (2) (Box-folder 11/11)
  - FL with cast of German production of My fair lady, 7"x8" (2) (Box-folder 11/12)
  - FL receiving honorary degree, 8"x10" (6) (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Snapshots on the Riviera and yacht (53) (Box-folder 11/14)